right we alive I'm going live today
because my iPad is plugged in for my
road trip and I don't want to record on
that and it's just something to put to
do for today thought this might be a
good thing to do weekly give a weekly
update as to what I'm up to what the
cooperative's up to it just still is
just me so let's see how that goes um I
don't know what's update probably should
make notes before I started this live
and learn I'll do that next week but how
we're creating a better world make
mistakes learn for them grow as my brain
wants to catch up in the lower much
different my glasses on contacts in from
the road chip huh going away I wasn't
gonna post anything today but I thought
I've been giving myself six days of
posting within a seven days it ends up
being on Sunday that I don't post that's
actually perfect cuz we're going on
today and coming back on Monday so I can
do this today and Monday as long as I'm
not comatose I will also post a quick
one and who knows maybe I'll even do one
for Sunday I feel so inspired if
something hits me I was gonna do one
today on being actually autistic but I
want to put a little more thought into
that one and make some notes and because
I got into a discussion debate this
morning with someone who was a mom to an
autistic boy and talking about the like
hashtag actually autistic and one of the
things was like self diagnosis is not
okay it's dangerous and I was like well
actually and so I want to talk about my
self diagnosis and why I think self
diagnosis is empowering and right and I
don't just feel that way about autism I
feel that way about basically anything
that is considered if you're just gonna
check off symptoms in order to diagnose
someone why can't the person do it
themselves I know that flies in the face
of our medical expertise and the
hierarchy doctors just to have over our
lives and over our diagnosis ease and
yes that is what I intend to do that is
absolutely I plan on putting more power
back in the hands of patients over our
own bodies
that doesn't mean discounting doctors
but it does mean flipping the
because a doctor said it when they can't
even all agree which is whatever that's
a whole I was also gonna this week do a
welcome to my brain video this is my
brain story this is its journey this is
what I can and can't do and I will also
be doing that one in the next week
hopefully I also want to put more
thought into that they're very tied
together having but the co-operative
itself I feel like for the first time I
was talking about this at dinner the
other day I'm like I'm so happy my
youtube channels getting actual like
comments my subscribers went up by 10
which when you're in I had it at 24 so
long and then finally this last week I
got like 10 which is like a 30% increase
and is amazing I mean even gotten 13
whatever that's not the point the point
is is to allow myself to be happy even
with that not to tie my sense of self in
any way towards how much traction I am
getting on social media with this idea
because I get that social media
platforms aren't designed to create a
world-changing idea they're designed to
have one go viral if you have it in a
perfect presentable package maybe but
even then they're not designed to have
people sign up for it be a part of it
and that is what we are doing we are
going to create the global cooperative
that focuses on creating the technology
we need to collaborate focuses on the
technology we need to live our best
lives by giving people the tools to be
able to come to a table and say hey this
isn't what's not this is what's not
working for me in my life how can I make
it work
whether that support groups whether
that's brainstorming tech solutions that
actually like I'm not eating healthy
well there's you can have there's nearly
infinite ways to help you with that
focusing on which ones are gonna impact
most people focusing on which ones you
want to co-create together with other
people is what we're gonna be able to
give people and then even in that one
area of being able to eat better and
having access to better food we all get
access to most of the solutions that are
created some of the solutions might
decide that they don't want other people
in them they
only want the people who co-created it
together but most of them will be yeah
we created this come on board bring we
don't want to keep diluting our efforts
so if we create a food app we don't want
everyone to have to create a food app
we're not gonna spend our pool of money
on that we're not gonna spend our pool
brainpower on that but having one and
then having um add-ons that we can add
that are more niche that are more um
like we want one pool of recipes we
don't want each one to have to redo
every recipe we want one pool of
information when you input products yet
we can still have it have individual and
yeah I'm gonna explain that right now
because coffee
I am excited by the idea of this thing
going somewhere no mic I've been doing
it for a really long time but I've had
the feeling that once I was able to
focus on the YouTube channel
authentically without it being something
that I felt forced to do and that has
now occurred like I'm like okay postie
and daily works for me and because I'm
posting daily some of them are getting
views and because I'm posting on other
people's channels some of them are
coming here and and subscribing and so
that is what I'm going to continue doing
once we get to the point where there are
consistent comments and discussions I
can ask a question and assume people are
going to respond in the comments and we
can have a conversation about a
conversation we can problem-solve
promise off and problem-solve in the
comments we can upload each other's
things that we think are our solutions
this platform is not designed to do what
we are going to design one to do but I
can use it to the best of my ability and
it is fairly good I've been using
periscope and I've enjoyed that but it's
not like people watch the replay and
they can't comment they can't say
anything it's not designed even as well
as YouTube is for this this um what I'm
what we're doing and the more I'm able
to interact with people online I'm able
to hone my idea I'm able to grow as an
end
to become the person who I need to be to
create this idea and more people hear
about it and want to come and be a part
of it even if I don't currently know
what that looks like I'd like someone oh
if that is one of the updates attended
an update it's a great update um someone
is creating a website for me I've said
it on several videos but why not explain
it during a weekly update one that I put
an ad on Craigslist saying like I need
someone to make my Wix website into a
WordPress one I don't have money and
there's a bit of my vision and so she is
creating that she's creating it for free
which is amazing it goes there's an
alignment with everything we are doing
together tapping into what people are
here to do often requires less payment
every time requires less payment than
creating something that people need to
get payment for the incentive of money
for work is a incentive it is not the
only one and it's not even the best one
for most people and I've also I wrote
the FA cues that a lot of people have
commented on things in the last few
weeks and ongoing that were the same
they bring up the same issues again and
again so I'm like okay that was the idea
of having the FAQ on the website but
I've never actually written enough that
just says hey please submit questions
and no one has submitted them in that
format but they have submitted them
online as I've talked about it I'm
saying hey like I tell you the many
amount of times but like tech is the
problem not the solution I'm like we're
on tech having that conversation so
what's the option we let it continue as
it is week or whatever that'll be in the
FAQ so I'm gonna try doing videos on
each of the FAQ s so that one there's I
can put that on the website itself if
people would rather watch a video as I
often would um and also just so they're
on video people never want to go to the
website they can see what the what
videos to watch that more topic yeah so
I decided I was giving the center ten
minutes I don't ramble the last ten
minutes if this one
a non live video I would redo it
and keep it to two minutes but it isn't
and it is what it is right now and I
will see y'all on Monday take care
please like and subscribe and a better
worlds on its way